迈克 · 诺斯: 我们已经稍微谈到了对象。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: We've already
touched on objects little bit.
它们有点像对象类型，它们看起来有点像对象值,
They're kind of, object types here,
they look kind of like object values,
只不过你用的不是键值，而是键类型。
except instead of key value,
you have key type.
我使用 Prettier 格式化我的代码，这就是为什么我在这里得到了分号。
I use Prettier to format my code,
which is why I get the semi-colon here.
我喜欢这个，因为看看这个，事实上这里有一个分号
I like this because looking at this,
the fact that there's a semi-colon, it's
还有一件事情能帮助我理解，这不是一个值，这只是一种类型。
one more thing that helps me understand,
this is not a value, this is just a type.
Mike North: 默认情况下，所有属性都是强制的。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: By default,
all properties are mandatory.
因此，我们在这里得到一个错误说，街道名缺少类型 houseNumber。
So we get an error here saying,
streetName is missing in type houseNumber.
我这里有一个错误的例子,
Well, I've got an example
of the error done here,
在这里没有街名，但是在类型中它是必需的。
streetName is missing in this but
it's required in type that.
我希望你们把它想象成等号的打字稿,
And I want you to imagine this as
TypeScript at that equal sign,
试图找到一种方法，使左手边
trying to figure out a way to
make the left hand side and
右手边的人同意，这些类型相容吗？
the right hand side agree in terms of,
are these types compatible?
在右手边，我们只有后生编号，在左边，街名，所以
On the right hand side, we just have
houseNumber, on the left, streetName, so
这就是为什么你看到的错误消息是这样表示的。
that's why you're seeing the error
message represented in this way.
如果你真的想做一些可选的事情，这并不是一件坏事,
If you really wanted to make something
optional, and this is not a bad thing,
我通常使用这个函数，如果我有一个大的选择包,
I typically use this if I have
a function that takes a big options bag,
大期权目标。
big options object.
用问号就行了。
Just use the question mark.
问号就像它可能在那里，也可能不在那里。
Question mark like it may be there,
it may not be there.
你看，我们并没有遇到这个问题。
And you see here we don't
run into that problem.
我们完全可以加上去。
We could totally add it.
麦克 · 诺斯: 我需要一个逗号。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: I need a comma.
街名，就是这个。
streetName, there it is.
Mike North: 所以街名就是空字符串,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So
it's just streetName is empty string,
这是个非常高级的地址。
it's a pretty exclusive address.
但是如果我想要另一个字体上没有的东西,
But if I wanted to have another thing
there that's not present on the type,
我会因此而破产的。
I'd be busted for it.
没有 x，你为什么要把它放在那里，对吗？
There is no x,
why would you put it there, right?
迈克 · 诺斯: 我们将深入探讨接口的细节。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: We'll go into
interfaces in pretty deep detail.
现在，我只想让你把接口想象成一个名字
For now, I just want you to think
of an interface as a name for
我们正在建造的这些结构之一，对吗？
one of these structures
that we're creating, right?
现在，您可以认为它只处理对象类型。
For now, you can think of it as
only working with object types.
我们还可以做一些其他的事情来使它适用于函数之类的东西。
There are other things we can do to
make it work with things like functions.
但我们现在要做的就是创建一个名字地址,
But all we are doing here is we
are creating a name, address,
我们可以在任何地方使用之前使用过的类型。
that we can use anywhere that
we were using a type before.
您可以从模块中导入和导出接口，就像导入值一样。
And you can import and export interfaces
from modules just like values.